 {

      "category":
            "Actors and Actresses",
      "questions":
          [
            {
               "answer": "Jared Leto",
               "question": "Which actor is the lead singer of a famous American band “30 Seconds to Mars”?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Dolph Lundgren",
               "question": "Which actor played the role of a Russian boxer, Ivan Drago, in “Rocky 4”?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Jeremy Renner",
               "question": "Which actor is well-known for his roles in “The Hurt Locker”, “The Bourne Legacy”, “American Hustle””?"
            },
            {
               "answer": "Nicholas Cage",
               "question": "Which actor appeared in famous films, such as “Gone in 60 Seconds”, “Face/Off”, “Ghost Rider“.?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Woody Harrelson",
               "question": "Which actor was cast in “Kingpin” - a famous 90’s comedy.?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Pierce Brosnan",
               "question": "Which actor played James Bond in 1990?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Vinnie Jones",
               "question": "Which actor used to be a professional soccer player?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Anthony Hopkins",
               "question": "Which actor played the role of a famous fictional serial killer Hannibal Lecter."
             },
            {
               "answer": "Robert Pattinson",
               "question": "Which actor played the role of the most famous contemporary vampire?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Daniel Day-Lewis",
               "question": "Name a famous actor with 3 Oscars for the films “My Left Foot”, “There Will be Blood”, “Lincoln”."
             },
            {
               "answer": "Elijah Wood",
               "question": "Which actor played the famous hobbit - Frodo?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Chris Hemsworth",
               "question": "Who is the most famous Hemsworth brother?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Hugh Jackman",
               "question": "Who played Wolverine?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Keanu Reeves",
               "question": "Despite his fame, he is often seen sad and completely alone on the streets."
             },
            {
               "answer": "Denzel Washington",
               "question": "Which actor was awarded Oscars for the films “Glory” and “Training Day”?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Orpah",
               "question": "What is the real name of Oprah Winfrey, a famous American TV host?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Bryan",
               "question": "Marilyn Manson’s real first name."
             },
            {
               "answer": "Cincinnati, Ohio",
               "question": "Actor Jerry Springer, famous for his roles in “Sunset Beach” and “Four funerals and a wedding”, was the mayor of which town?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Dunkin Donuts",
               "question": "Which coffee chain did Madonna work at?"
             },
            {
               "answer": "Chuck Norris",
               "question": "Which actor traveled with the circus at the age of 15 and was a tamer?"
             }
          ]
    }